New school year starts today, and so does my year in a third-year classroom.
I guess I'd better see which class I'm in.
Oichi, you wound up in the same class.
With me, I mean.
Oh, goody.
I can tell you're thrilled.
I've spent a lot of time not thinking about our class placements.
But I mean, even if me and Yamada wind up in different classes, the school's not that big a place.
What happened to keeping distance?
Um, whoops, the wrong person.
I meant Hey, Remyo.
What?
No way anyone's falling for that.
Gotta keep our distance in crowded spaces.
That's our new mission for the year.
But I mean, it is kind of weird to distance ourselves
if we're not dating in the first place.
We're back in class together again!
My goodness, Ana sure gets in everyone's personal space, though, doesn't she?
Sure does.
Gets all hands-on with everyone, too.
Just the cover-up we needed.
Even with all the boys. Touchy, touchy.
Stop what?
Got a problem?
I do not.
Oh, yeah!
It seems that I'm...
What?
I'm in the same class!
Um, yeah! Your name's right below mine, so I already knew who you were.
Yoshida generally comes after Yamada.
Hooray!
Embarrassing.
Huh?
Gee!
It seems that I have been held back a year.
Huh?
She can't face the brutal reality of her name not being on the class one list.
That's not it!
Ah!
Bunny's not anywhere!
Hold on, does that mean you transferred somewhere else when none of us were looking?
What?
Nothing we can do about that.
Nothing at all.
Oh!
Don't leave me!
Kobayashi.
Wait a second.
Hang on a minute.
Ah!
There you are.
And?
You're in class one.
Oh, thank goodness!
Sorry, that's on me.
Let's get to class.
Hey!
You did this on purpose, Mr. Maeda!
I know you did!
Let's get your shoes sorted!
Tell the truth!
Oh, what's up, Ichikawa?
Huh?
Upset about your class?
No, not really.
It's fine.
Just felt bad thinking you might have pulled some strings.
You see that, sir?
I told you he'd be just fine after a little while.
All right.
I'm guessing this is our new classroom.
Even more exciting after the runaround.
Oh, what's up, Ichikawa?
Huh?
Upset about your class?
No, not really.
It's fine.
Just felt bad thinking you might have pulled some strings.
You see that, sir?
I told you he'd be just fine after a little while.
All right.
I'm guessing this is our new classroom.
Even more exciting after the runaround.
We're back now.
Welcome back.
Oh, wow!
Roo and Mewka are here, too!
Basketball girls.
Oh!
Moipi!
Oh, wow!
Kan Kan!
Back together after a whole year!
Urena's here, too!
Remember karaoke?
Huh?
Moipi.
Kan Kan.
Serina.
Moipi.
Kan Kan.
Hey, y'all!
I'll be your new teacher!
Ready for Moriya?
My name's Moriya!
Well, guess it can't hurt.
Might as well enjoy our time in this tiny little place.
Ha ha ha!
Hmm…
Rest in peace.
Been waiting for you!
I'm pretty jealous of you, man!
Why's that?
How's class one, Ichikawa?
You make friends, you see any frilly panties,
cop-a-feeling any boobs, make eyes at all the girls?
This isn't some pervy rom-com, dude!
Come on! It must be nice in class one!
You've got Yamada and Hanzawa!
Plus, you've got last year's class two leader, Ando, in there as well!
Oh, it goes at the top of the hierarchy!
What are you, an NPC that explains the game setting?
Listen, on the way home, me and Oda from class two
are gonna need you to spill the deets on class one,
including any panties you see!
What now?
Staying for club?
We're third years now!
Yeah, uh-huh...
Hardly feels real...
Why did you want me to hang back?
Oh, right! Here's why!
I've been wanting to give this to you!
Wow!
Happy birthday, Kyotaro!
No, silly!
This is a wallet chain!
Tell me, though!
With three whole classes, how'd half the old class three end up here?
Yeah, dunno!
All last class two kids got along so good, too!
Oh, and hey!
Is Yamada going out with that Ichigawa kid?
Dunno!
Tell them no!
They're a problem if they are!
There are no rules on that stuff for Ana!
Why would there be a problem?
Stuff like this calls for a big celebration!
In class two last year, there were two kids crushing on each other!
So the class two last year, there were two kids crushing on each other!
So the class two didn't have to be a problem!
How'd half the old class three end up here?
Yeah, dunno!
All last class two kids got along so good, too!
Oh, and hey!
Is Yamada going out with that Ichigawa kid?
Dunno!
Tell them no!
They're a problem if they are!
There are no rules on that stuff for Ana!
Why would there be a problem?
Stuff like this calls for a big celebration!
In class two last year, there were two kids crushing on each other!
So the class threw together a flash mob and managed to get them to ask each other out!
We also got them to sing and dance together at our school festival performance!
I wanna do all that stuff again!
That sounds like literal hell on Earth!
That may be so, but those two broke up over the school break.
What?
No way!
Maybe we should've celebrated more?
Listen, KonKon.
Flash dance mobs and stuff.
Sounds like a lot of fun!
We'll have a ton of confetti to throw with them!
Party poppers?
Hey!
You bet!
Maybe even a confetti ball!
Huh?
Are we going together?
Um, that's what they were wondering, right?
Uh, I think...
Whoopsie!
Forgot to...
I am so done covering for you two!
How'd it go, Ichikawa?
Did you see any cute undies?
More like I showed mine.
I'm so freakin' jealous of class one!
Is Sekine also in class one?
For real?
Who even cares?
Who do you like best, huh?
Which girl grabs ya?
In what world do you think I would even get a choice?
Just wondering how you feel about your new class being the center of school hotties.
Didn't think much of it at first, but it feels pretty nice having everyone be jealous of me for once.
You're a real a-hole.
I'm in class one as well.
What?
You are?
I snuck off to see Hara who's in class two during all our breaks.
They got separated then.
I couldn't believe it.
She looks even prettier after she's away for 45 minutes.
You make it sound like she moved to the city.
I kinda get excited seeing how she changes with her new class.
There you go, getting creepy again.
Although for real, it must be pretty nice getting to be with Yamada again.
Yeah, I guess.
Why's that?
What?
N-no reason!
She's just so pretty to look at in class!
Like you ever thought that, man!
Because Yamada and I happen to be good friends.
Uh...
Okay...
I think the reason I didn't want to brush it away like usual...
That's all I want!
Mm-hmm!
What's up?
Gonna head off here.
Walk home with us sometimes, okay?
It might be because...
I think of Adachi as my friend.
Only sometimes...
Sam!
You're pretty busy, huh?
And so, the new school year began.
You're cheating, aren't you, Kobayashi?
Wow, you aren't!
Just using my key to get taller!
Is that so?
Next!
Good idea!
Gotta use my key for this!
Sucking it in doesn't change anything.
Today's our health check for the new year.
Ugh...
No luck, it seems.
Don't worry about it.
Let's see.
Hey, now!
Show me yours!
I told you not to do this with people around.
You're the one who freaked out and made a big fuss.
Celebration Girl here is the one who forced kids into an Ask Out event from hell.
The one person I don't want knowing how I feel.
I am not going to get forced into asking her out like that.
Are you two?
Pee?
Pee apparently signifies a significant relationship.
No.
W-weren't you listening to what Ms. Moria said?
I want everyone to spend the month of April talking to folks they don't usually chat with on the norm.
I want to see all of you make at least 100 friends.
Alright class?
This is just for good grades.
You know?
Yeah?
I haven't really talked much with Yamada either.
Oh that's true.
You can call me Kan-Kan.
How about Kana?
Why?
Because I want to have a name that's special just for me.
Ugh!
Hair this long and it's still kept so nice.
My heart.
Quit shooting straight through the heart.
Touchy touch.
Ugh.
I call her by the name Kana.
I'm sorry.
Sorry guys.
Yamada can be a little too friendly.
Me and Hanzawa used to get along good back in elementary school.
Sure did.
What is she, your ass?
In that case, how about I call you Panda instead?
In what case?
Sheesh.
I'm gonna call you Yamada A then.
Sure, that's fine.
Seriously?
Yamada A.
Panda.
Yamada.
I didn't say the A part yet.
And like always, I'm left alone.
Hey, what you up to?
It's nothing.
I just noticed I can finally reach a whole shelf higher.
You've shot up a lot, huh?
Six centimeters.
Hm.
Since last year.
Ah!
Incredible!
But you know, I actually grew 15 centimeters when I was in fifth grade.
Could you maybe not tell me stuff like that?
See, this is just one milestone of many.
You sound like an athlete.
Huh?
What is it?
Well, I was just thinking.
I want to mark it down.
You already have it on record.
No, that's not what I mean at all.
Wait, I know.
What?
I just remembered.
People used to mark their kids' heights on the walls at home.
So go stand over there by the wall.
Huh?
Hang on.
You can't do that.
It's permanent, right?
Uh, hmm.
This one's washable.
If we write it somewhere obvious, it'll just get erased.
That's a good point.
Oh!
Okay, now just stand still.
Right around here.
Yes!
Do you not even feel bad about this?
No, you mark me off next!
Take down the books up there, then.
I thought you said you could.
I'm going to get a chair.
Is your voice done changing?
What?
Yeah.
I don't know.
Let's see.
How far are we?
Hey, wait!
Twirly, twirly, twirly!
I used to think that I didn't want to ever grow up.
I didn't want to change and become somebody else.
But now, I do want to grow up and be closer to you.
Physically, I mean.
I don't mind.
Not at all.
Hmm?
I meant physically, like, height.
I'm sorry.
I want to tell her myself.
I know how much cave that needs.
you know, man.
I want to enjoy her self-large as I am and see you.
I don't mind.
In May I don't think it is the purpose of her life at all?
Amen.
Oh?
no reaction maybe she's not into romance then again we didn't actually do anything
maybe i'm overthinking things hey were you about to tell me something oh um i was
wasn't ready for that hey she dropped something
a book about deep sea fish it's not a library book her name's on it i'll bring it back to her
the next day our first seating change of year three i don't care where i sit what i do care about
is yurine hansawa she's best friends with celebration girl my biggest threat
she looks like she probably isn't the sort to go rat us out but never say never
hmm this is the spot the main characters always get yamada yeah my eyesight isn't
all that great mind if we switch seats for this round sure thing
good good come on i do not need this i always end up pushing back when people set me up like this
we're strangers gotta act that way
come on quit grinning
i'm next to anayamada hmm i suppose that's at least acceptable
what a story like the start of a love comic
hey lend me your book why should i how pathetic pulling away after we finally got so close
it's all too much
yamada left early today so we didn't get a chance to talk see you guys later what if i worry so much
about looking too close that we actually drift apart yamada might be sick of this act of distrust i'm
putting on that's hansawa's book it looks like she hasn't given it back yet guess i'll have to then
huh
a letter and yamada's handwriting i'm writing this because i think you have the wrong idea
ichikawa and i are really close but we aren't going out as of april 10th but that's not what i want to
clear up it's ichikawa see he's really very shy he's always thinking about other people to the
point where it gets hard to watch when i get close he draws away he's a lot like a cat but we've slowly
but surely built up our friendship even just bit by bit as awkward as it may seem the time we spent
and the closeness we have are really important to me so so i don't need you to worry about me
anymore i'd actually like it if you could just leave us be one day i plan to no i can't
i can't
morning
oh
the closeness we have is really important sorry for meddling with things it's fine
it's just that i want to know what love is meant to be like i guess
is it different from friendship different from admiration it's a good thing but we're not supposed
to celebrate it why did the pair from last year break up did we do something did we break them up
i'll teach you all about the ways of love if that's what you want
i i won't have it
you really gotta watch how close you get with people
but why though